istrategyconference.com 2014-05-26

# Privacy Policy

###  Privacy policy

The iStrategy Conference is strongly committed to protecting your privacy while interacting with our content, products and services in a safe and secure environment.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to tell you what kind of information we may gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct this information. Our policy allows you to choose what kind and how much information you provide to us and to control how we use whatever information you give us. Our goal is to provide you with a satisfying experience while allowing you to control your privacy and to give you a means to voice any questions or concerns you may have.

**Collection of Information**

Information is collected from you primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked to provide information such as your name, email address or information about what you like and do not like. It is entirely your choice whether to respond to these questions or not.

The iStrategy Conference website collects two types of information. The first type is anonymous information. For instance, we may collect information to tell us that five thousand people visit this Privacy Policy today, but we do not know their names, where they live or their date of birth - they are 'anonymous' to us. Another example of the iStrategy Conference website collecting anonymous information is when the iStrategy Conference invites you to respond to surveys on its website. The surveys may ask you for demographic information such as your age, gender and postcode. This information is collected for research purposes, is used in the aggregate (where possible), and remains anonymous. Many of the individuals who access our services are anonymous to us.

The second type of information that the iStrategy Conference website collects is personal information. The iStrategy Conference website will collect personal information that let's us know the specifics of who you are such as your name, email address, or postal address, when you provide it to us. With this information, the iStrategy Conference website can provide a variety of personalised and enhanced services that are not available to anonymous users. We hope that you will find it beneficial to provide individually identifiable information about yourself to us because it will make our services more valuable to you.

Sometimes, we may specifically ask for personal information about you when you sign up to use a service. Certain information may be required, such as your name, age, internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number, etc..., in order to provide that service or product to you. This information may also be used to inform you of additional products and services which may interest you. You can choose not to receive such information when you are undertaking product or service registration on our website. We may also ask about your interests, but it is your choice whether to respond. How much of your personal information that you choose to disclose to the iStrategy Conference is completely up to you. The only way we know something about you personally is if you provide it to us, for example when you take part in a discussion forum or enter one of the competitions on our websites.

**Use of Anonymous Information**

The iStrategy Conference website automatically gathers anonymous information to monitor the use of its website like the numbers and frequency of visitors and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our audiences use parts of the site, so we can improve the website to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many users as possible. The iStrategy Conference website may publish or provide this aggregate data to other people.

**Use of Personal Information**

The iStrategy website will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for which you provided it. We will not use it for any other purpose without your consent.

**Disclosure**

There will be occasions where it will be necessary for the iStrategy Conference to disclose your personal information to third parties. The iStrategy Conference may be required by law to disclose the information, or the iStrategy Conference may be required to disclose your personal information to third parties to provide the service you have requested, for example, if you purchase products online from the iStrategy Conference website, we will need to disclose your personal information to third parties in order to bill and deliver your products. However, the disclosure will only be made where it is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which you disclosed your personal information. Otherwise than stated above, we do not disclose personal information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any organization or person outside the iStrategy Conference server.com unless you have authorised us to do so. For example, when you contribute to an online forum you may want to publish your name and email address.

**No Sale of Personal Information**

Under no circumstances will the iStrategy Conference sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information.

**Interacting with the iStrategy Conference**

There are many interactive features on the iStrategy Conference website that you can contribute to. These include: Forums, Reviews, Online subscriptions, Community, Mailing Lists and Email.

When interacting with the iStrategy Conference, we suggest that you use your discretion and exercise caution when providing your personal information.

Note that whenever you post personal information in publicly accessible places, such as chat rooms or message boards, this information becomes available to anyone with access to the Internet. This information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Therefore, we recommend that you refrain from posting any information that you do not want seen in these public areas.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any personal information. Be responsible whenever you are online.

**Access and Correction: Personal Data**

If the iStrategy Conference holds your personal information the iStrategy Conference will where possible, provide you with access to the information. The iStrategy Conference will take reasonable steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up to date.

**Security**

The iStrategy Conference operates secure data networks that are designed to protect your privacy and security.

**Complaints about Privacy**

If you have any complaints relating to online privacy issues on our website, please notify the iStrategy Conference. While the iStrategy Conference accepts no liability for any material or links posted to the service, we will investigate all complaints.

**Changes to the iStrategy Conference Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change the iStrategy Conference Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here.

**Contact Details for Complaints**

Email [iteam@istrategyconference.com](mailto:iteam@istrategyconference.com?subject=Website%20complaint) or write to: Website Complaints Department The iStrategy Conference Queen Square House 18-21 Queen Square BRISTOL BS1 4NH United Kingdom
